{"data":[{"question":"Seven of planets rotate in the same direction as their orbital motions, while Venus and Uranus rotate in the opposite direction.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"of planets ","b":"as ","c":"while ","d":"opposite direction","answer":"1","explain":"- Of planets-> planets","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"The Millicent Rogers Museum houses five thousand pieces of Hispanic and American Indian jewelry, textiles, and other objects document the vibrancy of these cultures.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"five thousand ","b":"other ","c":"document ","d":"these cultures","answer":"3","explain":"- Document-> to document","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Languon Hughes's The Book of Negro Looksore is a too much valuable introduction to an integral part of folk literature of the United States.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"too much ","b":"to ","c":"part ","d":"folk literature ","answer":"1","explain":"- To much-> very","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"From 1866 to 1833, the bison population in North America was reduced from an estimated 13 million to a few hundreds.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"From ","b":"was reduced ","c":"estimated ","d":"hundreds","answer":"4","explain":"- Hundereds-> hundered","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"The Obie Awards have been given annually for 1956 to outstanding artists in off-Broadway theater.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The ","b":"for ","c":"outstanding ","d":"in ","answer":"2","explain":"- For-> from","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Along the East Coast, American Indian women's councils could veto a declaration of war at refusal  to supply moccasins and field rations.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Along ","b":"could veto ","c":"a declaration ","d":"at refusal ","answer":"4","explain":"- At refusal-> by refusing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Carrie Chapman Catt organized the League of women voters after successfully campaign for the constitutional amendment that gave women the right to vote.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"organized ","b":"after ","c":"campaign ","d":"that gave ","answer":"3","explain":"- Campaign-> campaigned","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Any group that conducting its meetings using parliamentary rules will encounter situations where prescribed procedures cannot be applied.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Any group ","b":"conducting ","c":"where ","d":"cannot be ","answer":"2","explain":"- Conducting-> conducts","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Even as he wrote copiously on such diverse topic as education, politics, and religion, Lewis Mumford  remained active in city and regional planning.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"wrote ","b":"diverse topic ","c":"remained ","d":"in city ","answer":"2","explain":"- Diverse topic-> diversified topic","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"For centuries the aromatic spices of the Far East has been in demand by the people of the East and West.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"For ","b":"the aromatic ","c":"has been ","d":"demand by ","answer":"3","explain":"- Has been-> have been","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"}]}